<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage of Ning Zhang</title>
    <link>https://ning6688.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Homepage of Ning Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 15:07:44 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ning6688.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Demos</title>
      <link>https://ning6688.github.io/demos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 15:04:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ning6688.github.io/demos/</guid>
      <description>coming soon </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ning6688.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 15:07:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ning6688.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>coming soon </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ning6688.github.io/posts/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ning6688.github.io/posts/home/</guid>
      <description>I am an assistant researcher at Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Shanghai Jiao Tong University.
Research Interest: Machine learning for audio analysis and generation, multi-media understanding, time series prediction
Google Scholar
Education 2011/09-2016/07 Institute of Automation, Chinese Academy of Sciences. PhD. Major in pattern recognition and intelligent system.
2007/09-2011/07 University of Science and Technology Beijing. Bachelor. Major in automation engineering.
Working Experience 2020/09-Present Assistant Researcher (SJTU)
2018/04-2020/08 Senior Staff Researcher (Kuaishou Tech.)
2016/07-2018/04 Staff Researcher (IBM Research)
###Some Publications
  Ning Zhang, Junchi Yan*. Rethinking the Defocus Blur Detection Problem and A Real-Time Deep DBD Model. European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV 2020). (Accept) (CCF B)
  Ning Zhang. Learning Adversarial Transformer for Symbolic Music Generation. IEEE Transactions on Neural Networks and Learning Systems (IEEE TNNLS).(Accept) doi: 10.1109/TNNLS.2020.2990746. (JCR Q1)
  Ning Zhang, Tao Jiang, Feng Deng, Yan Li. &amp;ldquo;Automatic Singing Evaluation without Reference Melody Using Bi-dense Neural Network.&amp;rdquo; IEEE International Conference on Acoustics, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP). IEEE, 2019. (CCF B)
  Ning Zhang, Junchi Yan*, Yuchen Zhou. Weakly Supervised Audio Source Separation via Spectrum Energy Preserved Wasserstein Learning. 4574-4580. IJCAI 2018. (CCF A)
  Ning Zhang, Yali Zang, Xin Yang, Xiaofei Jia, Jie Tian. Define a Fingerprint Orientation Field Pattern. 23nd International Conference on Pattern Recognition 2016 (ICPR).
  Ning Zhang, Xin Yang, Yali Zang, Xiaofei Jia, Jie Tian. Adaptive Orientation Model Fitting for Overlapped Fingerprints Separation. IEEE Transactions on Information Forensics and Security, Oct. 2014 (SCI IF=2.408)
  Ning Zhang, Xin Yang, Yali Zang, Xiaofei Jia, Jie Tian. Overlapped Fingerprints Separation Based on Adaptive Orientation Model Fitting. 22nd International Conference on Pattern Recognition 2014(ICPR). (Oral Report).
  Ning Zhang, Xin Yang, Yali Zang, Xiaofei Jia, Jie Tian. Generating Registration-Free Cancelable Fingerprint Templates Based on Minutia Cylinder-Code Representation. Biometrics: Theory, Applications and Systems (BTAS), 2013 IEEE Sixth International Conference on.
  Ning Zhang, Yali Zang, Jie Tian. The Integration of Biometrics and Cryptography-A New Solution for Secure Identity Authentication. Journal of Cryptologic Research, 2(2) 2015. (CCF B)
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>